Alright. Well, I went to the
zoo to find out more about the
way people exist with animals.
Animals with each other and
with people too. It probably
wasn't a fair test but with
everyone separated by bars from
everyone else but if it's a
zoo, that's the way it is. Move
over. I'm sorry, I thought you
had enough room. Well,
there. All the people, all the
children, everyone. It's a nice
day and all the animals are
there too. Move over. Okay, and
it's a hot day too. So, all the
stitches there too and all the
balloon cellars and all the ice
cream cellars and all the seals
are barking and all the birds
are screeching. Move over. Look
here, you have more than enough
room and I am there too and
it's feeding time in the lion's
house. One of the lion's houses
and one of the lion keepers
keeps coming in one of the
lion's cages to