And my memory of her is slight
except that I remember she did
all things dowerly. Eating,
sleeping, working, praying. She
dropped dead on the stairs to
her apartment. My apartment
than two on the afternoon of my
high school graduation. A
terribly middle European joke
if you ask me. Oh my. I mean,
oh my. Oh, you're what? But
that was a long time ago and I
have no remembrance of any of
it that I care to admit to
myself. Perhaps you can see now
though, my good old mom and
good old papa Franklin. What's
your name? Your first name? Uh
I'm Peter. I forgotten to ask
you, Peter. Peter, Peter,
Peter, pumpkin eater. I am
Jerry. Hello, Jerry. And let's
see now. What's the point of
having a girl's picture
especially in two frames? I
have two picture frames you
remember. I