The tensions are high. The
pressure is there. And all the
go and it's a good start by
Abhishek from the last game but
it's at the moment is Kush from
Bihar and Abhishek and they
have taken this level ah race
to another level. And Kush of
Bihar is going to win it and
Abhishek has come second. And
despite of putting his best of
the efforts, Nikhil could come
third only. A very good race
and all the fields did very
well in this contest. But it's
the winner in front of our
screen, it's Kush Kumar of
Bihar who won the race with the
timing of 11. 48 Abhishek came
second Nikhil came tired and a
legs under despite of putting
in lot of pressure. And lot of
power from his legs, he could
come at the last day spot. What
is that?
Larry.
I am
Yeah.
First contest ended. Just there
in which ah Kush of Bihar won
the gold medal. And then
Abhishek Chaudhary of Uttar
Pradesh came second, Nikhil
came third and Alexander pitch
of Tamil Nadu came fourth. Now
moving on to the next contest
and this is 100 meter dash for
women. And let me remind you
that in this contest we have a
representative from India in
world athletics meet Tuti
Chandy is there but ah she is
there and she is a star
attraction of this ah evening
and she must be looking to
improve her timings there
because ah by the timings of
lane. 26 she has qualified
there but currently she is
ranked fortieth and ah 48
athletes ah have to be there so
the timings are for the world
cup qualification mark is 11.
24 and she has ah clocked 11.
26 so she is currently fortieth
she must be looking forward ah
to improve her timings and ah
in the presence are five
athletes running in lane number
three and she is from Rajasthan
then we have another athlete
from Madhya Pradesh Hindu
Prasad who is running next to
her in lane number four then
Duti