Bango's the big bang then the
darkness and thunder Adam and
Eve were strands of bacteria
blind we crawled with the birds
and the bees a few years on we
climb down from the trees and
we're standing in Africa
looking at the sky saying why
we here what happens when we
die we use god as a word for
the things we can't see now
plant some clothes and let's
wait for TV well it doesn't
take long till we're paying in
caves making some men king and
other men slaves saying god is
our reason and god is our
leader god spoke to me and he
told me to kill you we spread
like a virus to every dark
corner Greeks and Romans are
laying down borders slaves and
the soldiers the queens and the
kings wherever they were used
to sing
weddings and wars that we are
good for if all of the past was
played as a song our lives are
a beat of the drum invading and
saving and trading the plunder
tobacco and opium tea leaves
and sugar empires built with
the bones of the slaughtered a
barrel of booze it return for
your daughters and burn the
weddings at war they songs they
sing jingle.
The same stars you can't hide
the beast that we
forgotten who's got the right
ones still singing and dancing
we're paying on canvas passing
the time with our sex and a
half island store.
Romeo and Juliet can't make it
work.
Someone invents the tea
can't hide the beast that we
are instead of hunting now we
go to Tesco's instead of
talking now we wear headphones
instead of mountains we're
heading for Mars instead of god
we have credit cards and we're
2thousand and some peace
economy's crashing singing and
dancing and looking at the sky
saying why are we. Happens when
we die
the past was great as a song
and our lives are a beat of the
drum and our lives are a beat
of the drum