Nothing to be done. I'm
beginning to come round in that
opinion. All my life, I've
tried to put it from me saying,
Vladimir, be reasonable. You
haven't yet tried everything
and I resumed at the struggle.
We should have thought of it a
million years ago when the
world was young. Stop
bladdering and help me off with
this bloody thing. Hand in hand
from the top of the Eiffel
Tower among the first. We were
presentable in those days. Now
it's too late. They wouldn't
even let us up. Oh. What are
you doing? Taking off me boot.
Did that never happen to you?
Boots must be taken off every
day. I'm tired telling you
that. Why don't you listen to
me? Help me. It hurts. Hurts.
He wants to know if it hurts.
No one ever suffers but you. I
don't count. I'd like to hear
what you'd say if you had what
I have. It hurts. Hurts. He
wants to know if it hurts. You
might button it all the same.