What do we do now? Wait? Yes,
but while waiting.
How about hanging ourselves? It
might give us an erection. An
erection with all that follows.
Where it falls, mandraids grow.
That's when they shriek when
you pull them up. Did you not
know that? Let's hang ourselves
immediately. From a barrel. I
wouldn't trust it. We could
always try and go ahead. Oh,
after you. No, no, you first.
Why me? You're lighter than I
am. Just so. I don't
understand. Use your
intelligence, can't you? I
remain in the dark. This is how
it is. The bell. Use your head
can't you? You're my only hope.
Go go light. Bow not break. Go
go dead. Dee Dee heavy. Bow
break. Dee Dee alone. Whereas.
I haven't thought of that. If
it hangs you it'll hang any