Did you see? And now you turn
him away. Such an old,
unfaithful servant. Wine. After
having sucked all the good out
of him, you chuck him away like
a like a banana skin. Really? I
can't bear it. Any longer. The
way he goes on. You've no idea.
Mister I'm going mad. You must
go. I can't pay getting longer.
Can't hear it any longer. He's
going mad. It's terrible. How
dare you? It's abominable. Such
a good master. Crucify him like
that after so many years,
really. You used to be so kind,
so helpful, and entertaining my
good angel and now, he's
killing me. Does he want to
replace him? I don't know. Ask
him. Gentlemen, I don't know
what came over me. Forgive me.
Forget all that I said. I don't
remember exactly what it was
but you may be sure there was a
word of truth in it.